In case you are interested, Ion is in charge of research and Sarah is in charge of photos.
I will mainly turn this video.
We are now looking at what to eat? I am looking at the opinion that
We are going to eat soba and danbo now.
Yay!
Bon appétit!
One by one
Trouble shoga!
Cold?
Cold.
Yes, sir.
I had udon noodles from the countryside.
They said it looked like me.
Hot prawns?
Rare.
Then I'm hungry.
Bon appétit!
Rare.
Are you sure? Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Really?
It's delicious.
Thank you for the food. It was delicious.
It's a great view. I'd love to come back when I'm on official business.
Hey! There was only a star.
Oh, what's that? Isn't that it?
You wanna go for a run? Running?
It's going away, it's going away, it's going away, it's going away.
Then let's leave it.
Where'd Saachan go?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Bye, Saichan!
I lied.
Ta-da!
The soot has arrived.
First of all, this is what I was looking for
Not this.
I'm already after this.
I want this dumpling set.
And Sara and I will have...
Soy milk latte.
and matcha green tea.
Bon appétit!
Which one do you want?
Let's go for one.
I'll go.
Let's go to Ise.
Oh!
I'm in.
Okay, then. Isn't this it?
Yeah!
Let's hit the stores.
Mmm.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God.
You got me?
Thank you for the dumplings.
Now we are going to Kiyomizu temple
Yay!
We're going on foot!
We're going to eat, so we're going to walk.
Here you go
I'll do my best
Oh no!
There are so many delicious-looking restaurants!
So many of these, and yet you eat them!
I'm still good.
I can't eat it. I'll eat it.
What? You can't eat?
You don't eat it, you eat it together.
You look like you're gonna eat it.
You eat it like it's delicious.
But when you eat it...
It's delicious!
You're eating it?
It was so, so, so good!
It's still getting late at night.
I'm going to go and have a tempo!
Bye bye!
It's beautiful.
The sky is beautiful!
Lyon is beautiful
Everyone is amazing!
Beautiful!
Listen to this... everyone is beautiful!
Sudden promotion!
Rolo, I told you I don't eat a lot.
I'm not going to eat a whole lot, I'm going to eat so much
Sora, you're a baby.
She can't eat much.
Pewtyverland
Sun Smike Polly
Pewty Bar
Clean Transtage
Yay!
Bon appétit!
Jump to say
Condiments
Oh, shit, I'll take pictures of everything, but...
I got it!
I got it
Oh, no.
I'm on the stairs where I shouldn't fall down.
Saratchi style
It's time for an intensive trip ahead of 13
of information systems.
There's no mugwort.
something Miu is so I can tell what it's from if you're not there.
Well, well, well
Ten yen what?
Ten yen eight.
I'll know when Japan comes
Megume Megume
Matcha green tea monbla is not rare?
Shiro-miso (white miso)
It's white miso?
Yes, it is.
Shiro-miso.
Shiro-miso?
Choron.
There's lots of shiro-miso.
Delicious!
What's this?
It's moistened. It's not like it's lacquered.
It's so crispy.
Hmm?
Mmm!
Mmm?
Delicious!
Vanilla seal of the Snowy Bridge.
We've arrived at Hyamsdellas.
Wow.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
You look amazing.
You're pretty.
You're cute.
I have a date.
I've got a mouthful.
Second floor.
I went under the car earlier.
I went to the second floor.
I went to the key big.
But I thought I'd like to do it.
Okay.
I was on the second floor.
Congratulations.
What's that? He's running.
Where's the second floor?
One.
Oh, my God.
Congratulations.
When you go in together
What's this feeling?
I don't know.
To sit with your mouth tight
You must meet with joy
To meet with joy and more joy
That's how I feel.
Yes, sir.
The usual tsukkomi.
How was it? Shimizudera
Aeon's Piranhas...
Kyoto is amazing
The atmosphere is really nice.
Play in Kiyomizu-dera town
I wanted to go in summer
And the view of the sunset...
It's perfect.
I can feel the nature
It feels good
It's money for the maras.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to bring you more.
I'm looking forward to it!
Kyoto is the best!
I love Kyoto!